{
    "id": "2156fe96774148b8b47dc13f3814b891",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ................................ get up early on Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have to",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a15ed83768c2406d8390016246fd7ebc"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ................................... play with fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "need not",
                "don't have to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "768b88bcbb80421c806415eb9a26130d"
        },
        {
            "question": "In my job I ....................................... travel a lot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "have to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e77b269a1584bb29b2d1f886168deae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t lend her your car. She .................................... crash it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3bc0167b422a45d087733cedb6e51904"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ..................................... work on Sundays?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "have to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b46e8e55d4a24303ae6a91dce09ded9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ................................... work this afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "don't must",
                "don't have to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "39653cb2222e4dcaab424060dfe4125c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ..................................... hurry up if you don’t want to miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "have to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "513e77b6923b4b26a9018170d89a911e"
        },
        {
            "question": "That ………………….. be a policeman in plainclothes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "must",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "971a51cc97f14fc9bfb0eabd5d99ed66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………. work from nine to five.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "have to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7f3a4ce45fb45c986ee94bd1e457a30"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is somebody at the door. Who ..................................... it be?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "723b6b7f9182489ba22edbed2da6684d"
        }
    ]
}